<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://darknoise.app/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://darknoise.app/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-15T10:32:43-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Dark Noise</title><subtitle>The official site of the Dark Noise app for iPhone, iPad, and Mac.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 3.2 - Interactive Widgets</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 3.2 - Interactive Widgets" /><published>2023-09-14T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-09-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_2"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/assets/press/promos/releases/dark-noise-3_2-interactive-widgets.jpg" alt="Dark Noise Interactive Widgets" /></p>

<p>Dark Noise 3.2 was released today with support for iOS 17 and all new interactive widgets.</p>

<p>Dark Noise widgets have been rebuilt from the ground up to support the all new interactive widgets in iOS 17. This means you can start and stop a sound right from your widget without needing to open the app.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/press/promos/releases/dark-noise-3_2-widget-screenshots.png" alt="Dark Noise Interactive Widgets" /></p>

<p>There are now 8 different widget’s to choose from, each with 12 themes you can configure between. The small widgets all work wonderfully with iOS 17’s new StandBy mode, making it easier than ever to start your favorite ambient noise when you go to sleep.</p>

<div class="presskit-video">
    <iframe width="100%" height="100%" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/riiWuoLxj1c" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>

<p>Dark Noise 3.2 is available on the App Store to <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dark-noise/id1465439395">download for free</a>. Dark Noise Pro is currently available for $2.99 a month, $19.99 a year with a 3 day trial, or a one time purchase for $49.99. Screenshots and promotional material can be found in the updated <a href="/press">press-kit</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/promos/releases/dark-noise-3_2-interactive-widgets.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/promos/releases/dark-noise-3_2-interactive-widgets.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 3.1</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 3.1" /><published>2023-04-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3_1"><![CDATA[<p>Dark Noise 3.1 was released today with a few highly requested features after the big 3.0 launch earlier this month.</p>

<p>What’s New:</p>
<ul>
  <li>There is a brand new <strong>Green Noise</strong> sound that provides an endless ambient noise in the same frequency ranges as nature.</li>
  <li>A new “Classics” section has been added to the noise selection view with some of the original sounds before they were remastered. This will include sounds that are more dramatically changed whenever a remaster replaces them so that people who prefer the original sound can still use them.</li>
  <li>On iOS, 3 new alternate app icons were added with the original flat icon design called “1.0 Purple”, “1.0 Black”, and “1.0 White”.</li>
</ul>

<p>Dark Noise 3.1 is available on the App Store to <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dark-noise/id1465439395">download for free</a>. Dark Noise Pro is currently available for $2.99 a month, $19.99 a year with a 3 day trial, or a one time purchase for $49.99. Screenshots and promotional material can be found in the updated <a href="/press">press-kit</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Noise 3.1 was released today with a few highly requested features after the big 3.0 launch earlier this month.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-icon-v2-cropped.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-icon-v2-cropped.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 3</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 3" /><published>2023-04-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-04-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-3"><![CDATA[<p>Dark Noise, the popular white noise app, is releasing Dark Noise 3.0 on Monday March 27th.</p>

<p>The biggest new feature in Dark Noise 3.0 is the introduction of a free tier. The free tier includes access to 8 free sounds as well as full support for infinitely looping sounds, Shortcuts, Siri integration, and the Timer feature. This means that you can now enjoy the best white noise app for free!</p>

<p>For those who want even more features and sounds, there is <strong>Dark Noise Pro</strong>. This optional upgrade unlocks over 50 sounds, the ability to create custom mixes, alternate app icons, and alternate premium themes. With Dark Noise Pro, you can customize your white noise experience to your liking.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/press/promos/dark-noise-pro-compare.jpg" alt="Dark Noise Tier Comparisons" /></p>

<p>Dark Noise 3.0 also begins the process of improving the experience of Dark Noise with headphones or nicer speakers. This update includes <strong>4 high quality stereo remasters</strong> of existing sounds: Rain, Thunderstorm, Beach, and Airplane Interior. Future updates will include more remasters as well as a new focus on increasing the variety of sounds in Dark Noise.</p>

<p>Users who purchased Dark Noise before the 3.0 update will have all current Dark Noise Pro features unlocked automatically. There may be features in the future that require Dark Noise Pro, but for now original users will get all of the same features Dark Noise Pro.</p>

<p>Dark Noise 3.0 is available on the App Store to <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dark-noise/id1465439395">download for free</a>. Dark Noise Pro is currently available for $2.99 a month, $19.99 a year with a 3 day trial, or a one time purchase for $49.99. Screenshots and promotional material can be found in the updated <a href="/press">press-kit</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Noise, the popular white noise app, is releasing Dark Noise 3.0 on Monday March 27th.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-icon-v2-cropped.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-icon-v2-cropped.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 2.5 - Welcome to the Mac</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-mac" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 2.5 - Welcome to the Mac" /><published>2021-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-05-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-mac</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-mac"><![CDATA[<p>Dark Noise is coming to the Mac! The sleek UI and large selection of ambient sounds you know and love are now easier than ever to use while you work.</p>

<p>Taking advantage of the Mac platform, a new innovative “adaptive toolbar” UI allows you to shrink your window into a Mini Player to keep Dark Noise quickly accessible while taking up very little screen space. Dark Noise for Mac also features full menu support with keyboard shortcuts to feel right at home on your Mac.</p>

<p>All of your favorite Dark Noise features are here including timers, custom mixes, widgets, and multiple themes. And with iCloud syncing, all of your custom mixes will automatically be available on your Mac.</p>

<p>Dark Noise is available on the App Store <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dark-noise/id1465439395">here</a> and Dark Noise for Mac will release on Tuesday, May 25th as a universal app including the iPhone and iPad versions. Existing Dark Noise customers will be able to download Dark Noise for Mac for free.</p>

<p>You can find the latest beta release <a href="https://github.com/charliemchapman/dark-noise-mac-beta/releases">here</a>.</p>

<div class="presskit-video">
    <iframe width="100%" height="100%" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wsMA6Du03J8" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Noise is coming to the Mac! The sleek UI and large selection of ambient sounds you know and love are now easier than ever to use while you work.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-mac-rounded_1024.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-mac-rounded_1024.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 2</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-2" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 2" /><published>2020-07-20T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-07-20T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise-2"><![CDATA[<h3 id="dark-noise-2">Dark Noise 2</h3>

<p>Dark Noise 2 is the next major evolution of the best ambient noise app on iOS. Mixing sounds has been the most requested feature since launch and I’m excited to announce it’s finally here! A lot of work went in to maintaining the simplicity and tight iOS integration Dark Noise is known for and I’m very proud of the results. Along with iCloud syncing, new sounds, new icons, and loads of bug fixes this is the biggest update to date.</p>

<h4 id="new-features">New Features</h4>

<p><strong>Create Mix</strong> • Build your own custom mix from any number of sounds. Mix multiple of the same sound for even more variety! Animated icons can be built using the new icon creator or images or animated GIFs can be imported from the Photo Library.</p>

<p><strong>iCloud Syncing</strong> • Custom mixes and favorites will now sync to all of your devices using iCloud! No need to sign in or configure anything, your data will simply follow you to all of your Apple devices.</p>

<p><strong>8 New Sounds</strong> • New sounds have been added to the Dark Noise catalogue for playing on their own or added to mixes including: Rain on Tent, Wind Chimes, Windy Trees, Seagulls, Lake, Ship Deck, Flag, and Lullaby</p>

<p><strong>iPad Pointer Support</strong> • Navigate Dark Noise 2 using a trackpad or mouse with full pointer support on the iPad.</p>

<p><strong>New Icons</strong> • Inspired by the new design of macOS Big Sur a skeuomorphic icon was added to the list of custom icons. And the new Launched icon is in honor of the podcast of the same name by Dark Noise developer Charlie.</p>

<p><strong>And More!</strong> • Bug fixes, improved shortcuts support, and a rewritten audio engine, and even a new “Auto Volume” experimental feature round out the biggest update yet.</p>

<p>Dark Noise is available on the App Store <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dark-noise/id1465439395">here</a> and Dark Noise 2 will release on Monday, July 20th.</p>

<div class="presskit-video">
    <iframe width="100%" height="100%" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/D4dbuYqoHmA" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Noise 2]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-app-icon-cropped.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-app-icon-cropped.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark Noise 1.0</title><link href="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark Noise 1.0" /><published>2019-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-08-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://darknoise.app/posts/dark-noise"><![CDATA[<p>Dark Noise is a delightful ambient noise app designed to be simple to use, with a lot of powerful features under the hood. Each of the 30+ high quality ambient noises feature a custom built animated icon that brings the sound to life.</p>

<p>Let’s be honest, an ambient noise app should play your noise and get out of your way as quickly as possible. Dark Noise was designed with this in mind.</p>

<p>Power users will enjoy faster access to Dark Noise with Siri Shortcuts integrations, Today Extension widgets, and home screen quick actions. Dark Noise features over 20 custom home screen icons and has alternate light and pure black themes.</p>

<p>Dark Noise 1.0 press kit is available <a href="https://darknoise.app/presskit-v1">here</a>.</p>

<div class="presskit-video">
    <iframe width="100%" height="100%" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q7BDtu9CkAI" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe>
</div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Noise is a delightful ambient noise app designed to be simple to use, with a lot of powerful features under the hood. Each of the 30+ high quality ambient noises feature a custom built animated icon that brings the sound to life.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-app-icon-cropped.png" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://darknoise.app/assets/images/dark-noise-app-icon-cropped.png" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>